Select the rectangle tool and draw a plate in the 2D window as the base plate of the bag.
Use the internal line tool to draw an internal line.
Create a sewing line on this line.
Adjust the position of the internal line, because later the top will be sewed into a thread channel.
When the plate is relatively large, you can loosen the plate to reach the required size.
Copy the plate and cut it to keep a thread channel plate.
Use the positioning ball to adjust this plate.
Place it on the inner side of the outer plate.
Create a sewing line.
Freeze the outer plate and let the thread channel be sewed together.
The size of the plate is relatively small here, so directly reduce the particle diameter to 8 to get the original curve.
And reduce the conflict thickness to make the plate tight.
Copy a set of plates and turn them over.
Make sure that the holes are facing the front.
Since there is no break point on the side, you can't sew directly using the thread section.
If you use free sewing, there is no way to absorb the internal line that has not been made.
So choose to align the inner line to the inner line of the plate and add points.
Then you can use the sewing line tool to sew.
Unlock the front and open the simulation.
Then unlock all plates and simulate briefly.
Then choose all the plates and place the bag on the ground to adjust later.
When the particle diameter is relatively high,
When the particle diameter is higher, the outer line of the plate will not be smooth enough
Reducing the particle diameter can get a smoother curve
At present, the seam of the bag is not round enough, it looks like there is an obvious fold
After hardening, you can see that it is smoother
Due to the hardening, a part of the fold effect will be erased, so choose to change the physical properties
By increasing the bending strength, you can make it smoother
Next, we need to make the drawstring effect of the bag
First, add a fixing needle
Fixing needle
Next, we need to attach the other parts
For the effect of tightening the force of the tail end of the plate
This is to add a fixing needle to the top and sides of both sides
and tighten the area.
Then delete the fixed pin and return the shrink to 100.
As the shrink returns, you can see that there is a fold in the previously fixed area.
You can see that there is a fold in the previously fixed area.
Then try to make the part of the middle string.
First, freeze all the boards except the top board.
Then use the positioning ball tool to pull the board away from the other boards a little.
Also leave a gap to pass the rope through.
Make a very thin board and use it as a rope.
Use the positioning ball tool to quickly position a board near another board.
Press the Shift key to place it evenly.
Use the positioning ball tool again to place it in the right place.
Then, to prevent instability, freeze the rope board and simulate it.
To prevent instability, freeze the rope board and simulate it.
To reduce the strength of the rope board particles and add a fixing pin to fix both ends.
Since all the other boards are in a frozen state,
you can simulate it again.
The curse still exists.
Then you can adjust the position of the rope through the fixing pin.
This lesson is over.
See you next time.
Bye.